alldownloads4u.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Alldownloads4u.Com

## Privacy Policy

### **Privacy Policy**

**At “Alldownloads4u.Com” we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is the information on what we receive and collect when you use “Alldownloads4u.Com”, and how we safeguard your information.**

**We never sell your personal information to third parties.**

**We may use your IP address to help diagnose any problem with our service and to provide better services for our visitors.**

**Cookies and Web Beacons –  We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. The ads may contain cookies which may be used by the advertising companies to better understand a visitor’s preferences and help them to display related ads. However, the cookies received with the advertisements are collected by the advertising company and we do not have access to that information.These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.**

**Email Addresses – We never share your email addresses with anyone.**

**Log Files – As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (airtel, bsnl, mtnl, tata etc…), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer, Firefox, Chrome), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.**

**If you have any questions about this Policy, or your dealings with this website, please feel free to contact us via email “admin@alldownloads4u.com”.**
